[{"answer": "You guys are such babies.  You want to go home, go.  Me, I'm not going to stop until I find the fucking motherlode", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "We're not gonna get busted", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Marijuana is illegal in my country, and I believe in yours, as well.  We must be careful", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Amigo, you bring me fift", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Oh, they weren't that bad.  I mean, they were kind of cute", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Relax, baby.  We're going to wind up like us", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Two years.  my friend, I can't wait that long", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "my friend, I went to the doctor.  I don't have two years", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Yes, my friend.  She was very pretty", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You mean the drug money?  Yes, I got it", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Just low", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Yeah, Dad.  I really did.  What am I gonna do", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Intriguing.  I see.  Would you like to know my crime", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "No", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Oh, come on, my friend.  If we are to be friends, we must trust each other", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Ah, yes.  The murder", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "What do you got there, my friend", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "What kind of project", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "my friend?  It's my friend", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Yeah, I'm out", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Yeah, I'm out", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "How are we doing", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "So, you are wanting to sell the cocaine for me in your country, my friend", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "As much as I can give you?  Ha ha.  Very good.  I like that.  Come, my friend.  Let us drive.  We have much to talk about", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "What do I think?  I don't want my answer to be influenced by what I want, so I'm going to have to say I don't know", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I want money", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Beautiful girls", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Keep them coming?  Ah, yes.  Ha ha.  You are right.  But money", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Hello", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I don't think so", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I don't think so", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Why are you smiling", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Why are you smiling", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I know who you are, that place. Mister my friend", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "It's good you came down, my friend.  We need to discuss a few things", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "He's not here, my friend", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I see.  I'm sorry about this, my friend. I'm not happy about this situation. It's bad.  You now know who your Brutus is", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "It is very difficult.  my friend makes me a lot of money.  If my friend goes so does the money.  You were an excellent teacher, my friend.  When the student has learned well, the teacher is no longer necessary.  We must remember we have wives, friends, familia.  Even familia that has not been born.  But sometimes, we must forget as well.  I am like you. I must teach the lesson.  We want to teach the lesson.  But we cannot.  We must remember that life is the teacher", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "It is very difficult.  my friend makes me a lot of money.  If my friend goes so does the money.  You were an excellent teacher, my friend.  When the student has learned well, the teacher is no longer necessary.  We must remember we have wives, friends, familia.  Even familia that has not been born.  But sometimes, we must forget as well.  I am like you. I must teach the lesson.  We want to teach the lesson.  But we cannot.  We must remember that life is the teacher", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Life will take care of everybody. Diego, me, you.  It is the teacher", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "She's angry.  It's all over the news", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "You're not going to trial", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "What are you doing here", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Well, here I am.  See", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Thre", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Alright.  I'll ask my friend, tell him it's for you.  I don't think there will be a problem", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "No.  I just kind of like the sound of it", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "that place", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "I don't believe you", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Swear on my life", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "I swear.  On my life", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "I swear on your life", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "What do you guys want", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "What about him", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Well, I got a call from my friend.  He said this thing with my friend is a disaster. He's giving up lab locations, names, bank accounts, he was very pissed off. my friend said to take him down.  His exact words were", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "my friend, he wasn't asking", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "Mr. my friend, do you know my friend", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "Do you see him here in the courtroom", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Shhhh", "docId": "Blow.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "I know, Dad.  I love you too", "qsentId": 60}]